villavu.com 2014-05-27

# SRL | Forums - Privacy Policy

**_What information do we collect?_**

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter any of the following:

  * Username
  * Password
  * Email Address
  * Date of birth

Any information that is provided in addition to the aforementioned will be completely optional and up to the user. 

We also log the IP address of all users that register and log into our forum as a security measure. We will not publicly display these addresses and only staff members are able to view them. We may also collect anonymous data such as what browser is used, which threads are viewed, etc.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**_What do we use your information for?_**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To enforce our terms and conditions, and prevent or detect hacking activities, security breaches or safety risks in connection with our websites  

  * To process transactions 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * Register a user account on our forums  

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  

  * To aggregate information to generate anonymous statistics regarding use of our websites. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person  

  * To disclose information to the extent required by law, court order, as requested by other government, regulatory or law enforcement authority, to protect or assist in protecting our users, systems or the public, or to otherwise enforce legal rights as determined in our sole and absolute discretion  

  * To send periodic emails 

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**_How do we protect your information?_**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**_Do we use cookies?_**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information)

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**_Do we disclose any information to outside parties?_**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**_Third party links_**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**_California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance_**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**_Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance_**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**_Online Privacy Policy Only_**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**_Terms and Conditions_**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://villavu.com/forum/content.php?r=4-ToS>

**_Your Consent_**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**_Changes to our Privacy Policy_**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**_Review, correction and deletion of information from our records_**  
If for data protection purposes you are concerned that the personally identifiable information which we hold about you is not accurate, or should you wish to have your personal information removed from our records, please see the Contacting Us section of this Privacy Policy.

**_Contacting Us_**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
